JAN EPHRAIM NINO TANJA

15201 AMSO STREET, POWAY, CA 92064

C: (858) 205-7281 | jtanja@ucmerced.edu

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A devoted and precocious leader with exceptional skills and an impeccably motivated nature. Several years under professional guidance with a desire to change the world. Innovative and multi-faceted student at the University of California, Merced. Seeking an internship or research opportunity to further facilitate my passions in the fields of both computer science and electrical engineering.

SKILLS

- Java
- C++
- BASH
- Python

- Javascript
- SQL
- Android Studio
- Microsoft Office

WORK HISTORY

MECHATRONICS, EMBEDDED SYSTEMS AND AUTOMATIONS LAB

Undergraduate Research Assistant | Atwater, CA | August 2015 - Current

- Platform team leader: Unmanned Ground Vehicle for Water Leak Detection
- Utilized MAVProxy, GPS, image processing, a telemetry series, and a Pixhawk flight controller to program (in C#) a fully autonomous drone which maneuvers through fields in order to spot pipe leakage. Learned about Python and the Linux OS.
- Twofold effect: to cut down on excessive water usage, and to decrease overhead costs.
- Drafted the proposal which lead my team to become one of several finalist teams at the 2015 Big Ideas Competition held at UC Berkeley. Won Honorable Mention with \$2,000 in grant money.

HACKMERCED

Volunteer Lead | UC Merced | January 2016 - May 2016

- Responsible for the recruitment of 50 viable volunteers of UC Merced's first hackathon.
- Helped plan HackMerced over a short span of five months.
- Designated roles for volunteers and trained them in two 2 hour meetings.
- Threw the 36 hour event alongside 8 other lead board members while maintaining the food supplies and numerous volunteers to help keep the environment clean.
- Donated leftover food to local charity in Merced.
- Compiled documentation of event.

ASSOCIATION OF COMPUTING MACHINERY

Outreach Leader | UC Merced | December 2015 - Current

- Responsible for hosting and helping at events, such as LAN Parties and weekly meetings.
- Attended tabling events where I would promote the Association of Computing Machinery and enthusiastically convince many to join.
- Accountable for turning in club dues and other financial aspects.
- Competed at SD Hacks, Cal Hacks, and HackingEDU.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE Computer Science and Engineering

University of California, Merced

Merced, CA | Current

- Deans List Recipient, Chancellors List Honoree
- Cumulative GPA 3.7
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jan-ephraim-tanja-634a44107